Charles Greeley Abbot Papers, circa 1891-1950s
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Charles Greeley Abbot Papers
circa 1891-1950s
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
Abbot, Charles G, (Charles Greeley), b. 1872
Personal Papers
6.43 cu. ft. (6 record storage boxes) (1 12x17 box)
Accession 86-161
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists mostly of Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (APO) Waste Books containing data from solar constant studies. Materials also include eleven letters from Charles Greeley Abbot to Frederick E. Fowle concerning solar constant studies at Mt. Wilson, California, 1906.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
Fowle, Frederick E. (Frederick Eugene), b. 1869; Abbot, C. G. (Charles Greeley), 1872-1973; Mount Wilson Observatory; Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory
Subject
Astrophysics.
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Manuscripts
- Box 1
  - APO WASTE BOOKS
  - #54 (Box 1 of 7)
  - #63 (Box 1 of 7)
  - #64 (Box 1 of 7)
  - #80 (Box 1 of 7)
  - #100 (Box 1 of 7)
  - #114 (Box 1 of 7)
  - #116 (Box 1 of 7)
  - #147 (Box 1 of 7)
- Box 2
  - #26 (Box 2 of 7)
  - #53 (Box 2 of 7)
  - #70 (Box 2 of 7)
  - #81 (Box 2 of 7)
  - #109 (Box 2 of 7)
  - #110 (Box 2 of 7)
  - #157 (Box 2 of 7)
  - #160 (Box 2 of 7)
- Box 3
  - #22 (Box 3 of 7)
  - #25 (Box 3 of 7)
  - #27 (Box 3 of 7)
  - #57 (Box 3 of 7)
  - #60 (Box 3 of 7)
  - #106 (Box 3 of 7)
  - #120 (Box 3 of 7)
  - #155 (Box 3 of 7)
- Box 4
  - Unidentified (1891, 1948-1952) (Box 4 of 7)
  - Unidentified #2? (April 14, 1898 - December 1899) (Box 4 of 7)
  - #22 (Box 4 of 7)
  - #61 (Box 4 of 7)
  - #71 (Box 4 of 7)
  - #126 (Box 4 of 7)
  - #137 (Box 4 of 7)
  - #138 (Box 4 of 7)
- Box 5
  - #65 (Box 5 of 7)
  - #67 (Box 5 of 7)
  - #69 (Box 5 of 7)
  - #79 (Box 5 of 7)
  - #98 (Box 5 of 7)
  - #101 (Box 5 of 7)
  - #115 (Box 5 of 7)
- Box 6
  - Unidentified (May 22, 1902 - May 29, 1906) (Box 6 of 7)
  - Unidentified (May 5, 1894 - November 1894) (Box 6 of 7)
  - Unidentified (August 1922 - November 1927) (Box 6 of 7)
  - Unidentified (June - December 1902) (Box 6 of 7)
  - Unidentified (December 1902 - June 1903) (Box 6 of 7)
  - Unidentified #2? (April 1896 - March 1899) (Box 6 of 7)
  - #17 (Box 6 of 7)
  - #23 (Box 6 of 7)
  - #102 (Box 6 of 7)
- Box 7
  - Miscellaneous loose waste book calculations (Box 7 of 7)
  - Eleven letters from Charles G. Abbot to Fred E. Fowle, Jr., May - October 1906 from Mt. Wilson, California. Also includes original data from solar constant studies. (Box 7 of 7)